stackry.com 2015-12-21

# Privacy policy | Stackry - US shopping, global shipping

Stackry, LLC and its affiliates (collectively, “we”, “our”, “us” or “Stackry”) is committed to your privacy.  This Privacy Policy applies to and governs data collection and usage on the Stackry website ([www.stackry.com](http://www.stackry.com/), the “Site”).  It is intended to describe for you our practices regarding:

  * The information we collect and the information we hold on behalf of our website visitors (“you” or “your”);
  * How that information may be used; and
  * With whom we may share that information

We encourage you to read this Privacy Policy carefully when using the Site, or when providing information to us through the Site.  You understand that by using Site you are accepting our practices as described in this Privacy Policy.

**Types of personal information we collect**

We collect and store personal information that you give us when you shop on our Site, register on our Site, complete an application, request a catalog, place an order, enroll in a promotional or rewards program, or send us an e–mail. This information may include your name, mailing address, e–mail address, telephone number, fax number, credit card number and expiration date, and other optional demographic information. If you respond to a sweepstakes or contest, we will ask you to verify that you are old enough to participate.  To the extent applicable, we also keep a physical record of the USPS Form 1583 that you delivered to us at our offices.

**How we use and share personal information**

We use the personal information we collect to process your orders, identify you within our systems, contact you if we have questions about your order, and notify you about new products, new services or promotional programs.

We share your personal information within Stackry, it affiliates and with third parties that perform services for us or on our behalf (for example, credit card companies, financial institutions, shipping companies, market research firms, etc.) and when, in our judgment, we believe it is necessary or appropriate to prevent fraud, injury, or harm to persons or property, to protect our rights or the rights of others, to comply with applicable laws and regulations, or as otherwise required by law. Personal information may be transferred in connection with a business transition, such as a merger, acquisition, or asset sale involving any Stackry business or asset to which the information pertains.  We limit the scope of the information provided to third parties, and we allow its use only for the purposes for which it was disclosed. 

**Special information for Site shoppers**

Cookies are pieces of data that a website transfers to a user's hard drive for record-keeping purposes.  The Stackry Site may use cookies to provide enhanced functionality on the Site (e.g., user ID and password prompts) and aggregate traffic data (e.g., what pages are the most popular).  These cookies may be delivered in a first-party or third-party context.  Stackry may also use cookies in association with emails.  While these cookies may be associated with personal information (such as your email address), we do not associate personal information with clickstream data.  Our Site also may capture limited information (user-agent, last URL requested by the user, client-side and server-side clickstream) about visits to our Site, we may use this information to analyze general traffic patterns and to perform routine system maintenance.

You have many choices with regards to the management of cookies on your computer.  All major browsers allow you to block or delete cookies from your system.  To learn more about your ability to manage cookies and web beacons, please consult the privacy features in your browser.

**How to let us know about your preferences**

Stackry provides customers with marketing and promotional materials via e–mail, mail, telemarketing, and fax. If you'd prefer not to receive these materials, let us know using the instructions included in the following Q & A:

**Q. How can I contact Stackry?**

A. You may contact us using any of the following options:

  * Send an e–mail to us at [Support@Stackry.com](mailto:Support@Stackry.com)
  * Fax us at 781-569-0222
  * Write to us at Stackry, LLC, 10 Micro Drive, Suite 100, Woburn, MA 01801.

**Q. How can I avoid receiving marketing materials?**

A. To remove your name from our marketing lists, please follow the instructions noted below.

  * E–mail – Click on the "unsubscribe link" located in all of our promotional e–mails (Requests to opt out of promotional e–mails will be honored within 5 business days.)
  * Postal Mail, Fax and Telephone – Call, write, or send an e–mail to Stackry, using the contact information provided above.

When submitting a request by telephone or mail, please be sure to include all of the contact information you have ever used or provided to Stackry even if it is no longer current, including:

  * All e–mail addresses
  * All telephone numbers
  * All names and addresses, including city, state, and zip code

**Q.  I'd prefer not to have my name and postal mailing address shared with other companies for marketing purposes. What should I do?**

A. If you'd prefer not to have your name and postal mailing address shared with other companies, let us know in writing via e–mail, fax, or letter using the contact information provided above. Please be sure to include your name and postal mailing address as well as specific instructions.

**Accessing and amending personal information**

It is important that our databases are accurate and current. To review and make any appropriate changes or deletions to information about you, please contact us in one of the ways provided above.

**Our Security Measures to Protect Information**

To help protect the privacy of data and personally-identifiable information you transmit through use of this Site, we maintain commercially reasonable physical, technical and administrative safeguards. We restrict access to your personally-identifiable information to those employees who need to know that information to provide benefits or services to you.

**Children’s Privacy**

Our Site is a general audience site, and we do not intend to market to or collect, nor do we knowingly collect, personal information from children under the age of 13.  Unfortunately, we cannot always determine the age of a visitor to our Site or the sender of an email.

**Conditions of Use, Notices and Changes to Our Privacy Policy**

By using this Site, you agree to the terms and conditions contained in this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to any of these terms and conditions, you should not use this Site or any Stackry benefits or services.  You agree that any dispute over privacy or the terms contained in this Privacy Policy will be governed by the laws of the Commonwealth of Massachusetts.  Any legal action or proceeding relating to this Privacy Policy or your access to or use of this Site shall be instituted in a state or federal court in Boston, Massachusetts.  You agree to submit to the jurisdiction of, and agree that venue is proper in these courts.

**Revisions to This Privacy Policy**

_We reserve the right to amend the Privacy Policy at any time, for any reason, without notice to you, other than the posting of the amended Privacy Policy on this Site. You should check our Site frequently to see the current Privacy Policy that is in effect and any changes that may have been made to it. The provisions contained herein supersede all previous notices or policies regarding our privacy practices that govern the use of this Site._

**Your California Privacy Rights**

California Civil Code Section 1798.83 permits customers of Stackry who are California residents to request certain information regarding our disclosure of personal information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes. To make such a request, please write to us at the following address:

Stackry - California Privacy Rights  
Legal Department

10 Micro Drive, Suite 100  
Woburn, MA 01801

Questions Regarding the Privacy Policy and Conditions of Use  
If you have any questions about our Privacy Policy or any concern about privacy at the Stackry or the use of this Site in general, please contact us in one of the ways provided above.

Last Modified: March 13, 2012
